YYeTs人人影视字幕组出品
更多原创字幕翻译 请登陆www.YYeTs.com
■
时间轴：godwuwen
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
翻译： vero  非燕  阿蘅阿蘅  猫中之王
后期： 孤帆  字幕总监： YY
■
校对： Beckett猫  Castle赛    后期：孤帆 字幕总监： YY
老爸老妈浪漫史
第七季  第二十一集
一个人住  感觉如何
So, how's living alone?
说来有意思
You know, it's interesting.
我刚搬进新公寓时
When I first moved into my new apartment,
我觉得不安
I was nervous.
这是我成年后的头一次
For the first time in my adult life,
没有室友同住
I didn't have a roommate.
但后来我突然发现
But then it hit me:
这是我成年后的头一次
for the first time in my adult life,
没有室友与我同住
I didn't have a roommate!
即使我一丝不挂地走来走去
If I want to walk around naked,
也没人会在意
nobody cares.
即使我把洗衣篮扔到
If I want to leave the laundry basket
客厅正中间
in the middle of the living room,
也没人会管我
nobody stops me.
即使我把打包回来的汤
If I bring home soup from the deli
在冰箱里放上两天
and leave it in the fridge for two days,
也没人会偷喝它
nobody eats it.
即使我做了愚蠢无比的事
And if I do something colossally stupid,
也没人会知道
nobody ever has to know.
人人都嘲笑
People make fun of the guy
每晚待在家里无所事事的人
who stays home every night doing nothing.
可事实上  这种人才是天才
But the truth is... that guy's a genius.
因为老实说  一个人没事看看电视
Because let's be honest, sitting around watching TV,
喝喝啤酒  啃啃排骨
drinking beer and eating ribs alone
是每个热血美国人求之不得的事啊
is what every red-blooded American would rather be doing at all times.
话是没错  可如果有人可以分享...
Yeah, but wouldn't it be better to have someone to share the...
我是说  难道你不觉得寂寞...
I mean, don't you get lonely without...
好吧  听起来的确很棒
Yeah, that sounds pretty great.
你是问  跟脱衣舞女约会最大的好处吗
What's the best thing about dating a stripper, you ask?
没有
Nope.
她只是问你要点什么
Just asked for your drink order.
告诉你跟脱衣舞女约会的最大好处吧
I'll tell you the best thing about dating a stripper.
给他一杯苏格兰威士忌就好
He'll just have a scotch.
可以逢人就说
Getting to say,
"嘿  我在跟脱衣舞女约会呢"
"Hey, I'm dating a stripper."
我要走了
And I should go.
该去上班挣钱了
Time to make the doughnuts.
make doughnuts 做甜甜圈/赚钱
更像是坐在蛋蛋上上班  挣着男人的钱吧
More like time to make some dough sitting on some nuts.
dough 面团/钱  nuts 坚果/蛋蛋
她是个脱衣舞女  而我在跟她约会
She's a stripper. I'm dating her.
我在跟脱衣舞女约会  巴尼赢了
I'm dating a stripper. Barney wins.
我送你出去
I'll walk you out.
你们要去哪里
Hey, where are you going?
昆茵要上班了  她是个...
Quinn needs to get to work. She's a...
我知道  脱衣舞女  我懂的
I know, a stripper, got it.
出租车
Hey, taxi!
我的女朋友是脱衣舞女
My girlfriend's a stripper!
泰德  猜猜我们周五晚要去哪儿吃饭
So, Ted, guess where we're having dinner Friday night.
金钱餐厅[法语]
Chez L'Argent.
我太激动了
I am so excited.
这家餐厅的位子我们订了好久
We've been trying forever to get this reservation.
稍等一下
Can you hold on for just one second?
你干嘛啊
What the hell are you doing?
没什么
Nothing.
你刚是说要尿尿吗
Did you say you had to pee?
没有
No.
不过还真有点想尿  我去了
But yeah, I do have to pee.
靠  这孩子最好长得超级可爱
Man, this kid better be real freakin' cute!
刚才这是怎么回事
What was that all about?
莉莉昨晚做了个春梦
Lily had a sex dream last night.
春梦  快说说
Sex dream? Do tell.
我当时在漆宝宝的家具
I was painting the baby furniture...
爽呀
Oh, yeah.
真爽呀
抓紧时间  马修快回来了
Hurry up, before Marshall gets home.
对不起  宝贝
I'm sorry, baby.
你刚在睡觉吗
Were you asleep?
所有怀孕的女人都会做离谱的春梦
All pregnant ladies have crazy sex dreams.
因为她体内荷尔蒙作乱
It's just her hormones going berserk.
她梦中在她双腿间"翻江倒海"的人是谁啊
So who's responsible for her rapid thigh movement this time?
我最爱的那次是她跟乔治・华盛顿开搞
Oh, my favorite was when she banged George Washington.
乔治・华盛顿  美国首任总统
我喜欢她跟比尔・考斯比
I liked the three-way
还有蓝精灵爸爸玩三人行
with Bill Cosby and Papa Smurf.
比尔・考斯比  黑人演员
smurf可代表任何字  这句话可理解为
he fucked the brains out of her
蓝精灵爸爸把她搞得死去活来
Oh, he smurfed the smurf out of her.
此处smurf off相当于jerk off
而且考斯还在一旁看着她打飞机
Yes, while The Cos smurfed off in the corner.
我们都记得  但问题是
We all remember. But here's the thing.
每当莉莉梦见和别人乱搞
When Lily has dirty dreams about other people,
她都会告诉我
she always tells me.
但是这次...
But this time...
听起来你做了个狂野的梦哦
Sounds like you had a crazy dream.
梦见什么了
What was it about?
接着她的脸变成了...
And then her face turned...
朱砂红的颜色
vermilion.
只是  你和我
Just... you and me...
打得火热  一男一女
gettin' it on, monogamously.
一"杆"一"洞"
Monoga-me-oh-my.
不是稍显尴尬的玫瑰粉
Not the rose quartz of the slightly embarrassed,
也不是略微惭愧的番茄红
or the tomato red of the mildly abashed,
而是朱砂红  为肉欲而感到羞耻的颜色
vermilion, the color of carnal shame.
这只能说明一件事
Can only mean one thing:
莉莉的春梦对象  是我们都认识的人
Lily dream-banged someone we know.
好吧  我被你逮了个正着
Okay, you caught me vermilion-handed.
其实  我在过去的五年里
The truth is, I've spent the last five years
一直试图侵入你老婆的梦境
trying to inception your wife.
《盗梦空间》是两年前才出的吧
That movie only came out two years ago.
什么空间
What movie?
你知道我会猜是谁吗
You know who I bet it is?
罗宾
Robin.
已经确认过了
Already checked.
我和莉莉去
Lily and I paid her a visit
世界新闻的新总部拜访她
at the new World Wide News headquarters.
我太激动了
And I'm so excited,
因为这家餐厅的位子我们订了好久
because I've been trying months to get this reservation.
稍等一下
Can you hold on just one second?
你想干嘛呀
What the hell are you doing?!
没什么
Nothing.
照片不错
Nice photo.
你的通行证也超大的吧
Your passport must be enormous.
先声明一下  这照片不是我的本意
You know, for the record, I didn't want this.
我不想这样  也不同意这样
Didn't want it, did not approve it.
真是超级尴尬呀
It's super embarrassing.
你好  默尔
Hey, Merle.
你们想上去看看我的办公桌吗
So, uh, do you guys want to come up and see my desk?
-好啊  看就看  -走吧
- Yeah, why not? - Come on.
证件
I.D.?
那人就是我
Oh. Um, that is me.
女士  恕我直言
Ma'am, with all due respect,
你比那辣妹看来老了那么一丁点
you're a wee bit older than that hottie.
看在上帝的份上
For God sakes.
我现在每天都在全国电视节目上露脸
You know, here I am, on national TV every day,
仍有人在我的巨幅照片旁
and still a guy who spends his whole life
守了一辈子的门口
sitting next to a giant picture of me
却认不出我是谁
has no idea who I am.
我的人生不止守门口  我还玩乐队呢
This isn't my whole life; I'm in a band.
我们会红的
And we're gonna make it.
孩子们  他们确实红了
And, kids, they did make it.
但这事之后再说
But I'll get to that later.
算了  我大概之后也不会提到了
You know what, I'm probably not going to get to that later.
他们只出了一首歌  还不赖  完毕
They had one song, it didn't suck, the end.
你总是说做记者不是为了出名
You always said it wasn't about being famous.
你只是想做靠谱的新闻  对吧
You just want to do solid journalism, right?
这个嘛
Yeah, well...
老娘当然想出名
Of course I want to be famous!
在加拿大  我是亮晶晶罗宾
In Canada, I was Robin Sparkles.
那可是个家喻户晓的名字
I was a cabinhold name.
可在这里呢
But here?
无需出示证件  默尔
Don't need to see your I.D., Merle.
所有人都认识你
Everyone knows who you are.
你是默尔
You're Merle.
他只在圣诞派对上演了个小品而已
He was in one skit in the Christmas party!
对了  泰德现在怎么样
Uh, by the way, how is Ted doing?
孩子们  还记得发生了什么事吧
Kids, you remember what happened.
我向罗宾表白  却惨遭拒绝
I declared my love, she turned me down,
我俩都搬出了公寓  现在...
we both moved out of the apartment, and now...
我跟他很久不联系了  自从我们...
I haven't talked to him since we...
断绝联系后
stopped talking.
他很好
He's pretty good.
很好
Pretty good?
昨晚  你还穿着紧身三角裤
Last night, you ate a box of Froot Loops
消灭了一盒果脆圈
in your tighty whities.
不  我消灭了那盒果脆圈时
No, I demolished a box of Froot Loops,
一丝不挂
fully nude.
对  "很好"蛮恰当的
Yeah, "Pretty good" works.
巴尼
Hey, Barney.
莉莉
Hey, Lily.
你知道这是怎么回事吗
Do you know what this is about?
我会想知道原因吗
Do I want to know?
不是你  抱歉  兄弟
No, sorry, bro.
该死
Damn it!
好了  该说我的事了
Okay, time for my stuff.
伙计们  我昨晚坐在家中
Guys, I was sitting at home last night,
突然间  我接到了圣的旨意
and all of a sudden, I had a piphany.
圣的旨意是...
And my piphany was this...
实际上  应该是"神的旨意"
Actually, it's, uh, it's "Epiphany."
泰德纠正巴尼的发音  但巴尼以为纠正的是冠词
不  泰德  我是特指
No, Ted, this is the piphany.
内容是
And here it is:
让  每晚  都成为传奇
Make... every... night... legendary.
伙计们  我们曾有过十分传奇的夜晚
Guys, we've had some pretty legendary nights.
可也有过平淡无奇的夜晚
But we've also had some nights that weren't so legendary.
说你呢  "泰德逼大家看《超级肥妻》之夜"
Lookin' at you, The Night Ted Made Us All Watch Norbit.
好莱坞喜剧片  主演艾迪・墨菲
艾迪・墨菲扮演胖女人  有问题吗
Eddie Murphy as a fat lady; what's the problem?
那肥婆是艾迪・墨菲
That was Eddie Murphy?
平淡无奇夜已经结束
The non-legendary nights are done.
从现在起  我们生命中的每个夜晚
From here on in, every single night of our lives
都将令我们永世难忘
will be a night we'll never forget.
就从今晚开始
Starting tonight.
准备好参加史无前例
Who's ready for the longest, craziest adventure yet?!
最长最疯大冒险了吗
craziest adventure yet?!
很好
Good.
弱兵都临阵脱逃了
The weak have been weeded from our herd.
准备好大干一场了吗  泰德
You ready to rock and roll, Ted?
我也要回家了
Yeah, I'm going home, too.
我预感接下来会玩变装
I'm sensing some costumes coming up here
所以我还是先走为妙
and I'd rather steer clear.
泰德  20年后
Ted, 20 years from now,
你孤家寡人  而我成了总统
when you're all alone and I'm President,
你不会记得坐在公寓里无所事事的夜晚
you're not gonna remember sitting around your apartment doing nothing.
你会记得的是今晚
What you will remember is that tonight,
这个夜晚..
this night...
是"组建墨西哥街头乐队之夜"
was The Night We Started a Mariachi Band!
一  二  三  四[西语]
Uno, dos, tres, quatro!
组建墨西哥街头乐队之夜
好  你说得对
Okay, you were right.
值得纪念的一晚
Memorable night.
没什么能比得上明天  朋友
That was nothing compared to manana, amigo.
因为明天将是...
Because manana is gonna be...
"吃遍菜单上所有食物之夜"
The Night We Ate Everything on the Menu!
吃遍菜单上所有食物之夜
真是值得纪念的一晚
A really memorable night.
可明晚...
But tomorrow night...
是"把马匹带进酒吧之夜"
Is The Night We Brought a Horse into the Bar!
把马匹带进酒吧之夜
好吧  可明天...
Okay, but tomorrow...
是"从自由女神像上蹦极跳之夜"
Is The Night We Bungee Jump off the Statue of Liberty!
从自由女神像上蹦极跳之夜
不要
Nope.
那晚是莉莉阿姨
That night was the night of Aunt Lily
和马修叔叔的豪华大餐之夜
and Uncle Marshall's fancy dinner.
还包括高级豪车接送哦
Complete with a fancy limo ride.
惊喜吧
Surprise!
你好
Hello!
你好  兰吉特
Hi, Ranjit.
不是吧
No.
要不从西区高速走
Should I take the West Side Highway?
随便你  兰吉特
Why not, Ranjit?
反正你总是随意抢走你想要的
Don't you always just take whatever you want,
从来不顾别人的感受
regardless of anything but your own
只顾自己下流恶心变态的喜好
dirty, sick, twisted appetites?
我还是呆在百老汇大道上吧
I'll stay on Broadway.
证件呢
I.D.?
天啊  张大你的...
For God's sakes, open your...
好吧  那就没辙了
Yeah, that's about right.
证件
I.D.?
罗宾最终吸取教训
Robin had finally learned the lesson
明白名气不是说来就来
that nobody gets famous overnight.
但离谱的是
But here's the crazy part:
就在那晚  她成名了
that night, she got famous.
罗宾  你在这里啊
Robin, there you are.
桑迪・里维斯
Sandy Rivers!
节目明星
Star of the show.
-你真相了  兄弟  -是
- What it is, my man. - Yeah.
罗宾  我给你安排了件"大"事
Robin, I've got something big for you,
超级"大"哦
something huge.
我想交给你"干"
And I want you on it.
桑迪  你可是上过骚扰丑闻视频
Sandy, you were in the harassment video.
不过你在里面表现不错
You were great in that, by the way.
谢谢  霍姆斯
Thanks, Holmes.
我很喜欢你小脑袋里的龌龊思想  罗宾
And I like the way your filthy little mind works, Robin,
但这不是开玩笑
but this is real.
重大事件播报
Big story's breaking.
你害怕坐直升机吗
Are you afraid of helicopters?
我爱坐直升机
I love helicopters.
-要我报道什么  战争吗  -比那更棒
- What am I covering, a war? - Better!
世界新闻带你看世界
World Wide News brings you the world.
现在由罗宾・施巴斯基播报道路信息
And now Robin Scherbatsky with traffic.
你不想去蹦极  那行
You don't want to go bungee jumping, fine.
今晚改成"从自然博物馆
Tonight's The Night We Stole a Mummy
偷走木乃伊之夜"
from the Natural History Museum!
从自然博物馆偷走木乃伊之夜
这个我也没兴趣
Yeah, I'm not doing that.
那把你的交通卡拿出来  泰德
Then get out your MetroCard, Ted,
因为今晚是
because tonight's
"与流浪汉狂欢之夜"
The Night We Partied with the Mole People!
与流浪汉狂欢之夜
巴尼  我冰箱里有一人份的史都华千层面
Barney, I have a Stouffer's lasagna for one in the freezer
那味道会让我回味无穷
that is going to be unforgettable.
我录像机里有《桑福德和他的儿子》
I have a Sanford and Son on my DVR
《桑福德和他的儿子》  80年代感人励志电视剧
个中感悟会让我铭记一生
that I will take with me to my grave.
我没必要让今晚比这样更难忘
I don't need tonight to be any more memorable than that.
《桑福德和他的儿子》听起来不错
Okay, Sanford and Son does sound good.
可如果我可以说出反驳你的话  那就是
But if I could just present a counter argument...
你被锁在外面了  傻子
You're locked out, dummy!
该死  巴尼
Damn it! Barney!
把电话给我  我要找管理员
Give me your phone; I'm calling my super.
唯一要打的电话  是打给所有我们认识的人
The only person we're calling is everyone we know,
因为今晚是"追踪菲尔・科林斯
because tonight's The Night We Tracked Down Phil Collins,
菲尔・科林斯和彼得・盖布瑞尔皆为英国著名男歌手
两人曾是创世纪乐队的团员
和他结为死党
Became Best Friends with Him,
并说服他和彼得・盖布瑞尔重组
and Talked Him into Reuniting with Peter Gabriel,
然后我们在创世纪乐队的新专辑里唱合音
so then we got to sing backup on the new Genesis album
一切超级棒之夜"
and it was awesome!
追踪菲尔・科林斯  和他结为死党
并说服他和彼得・盖布瑞尔重组
算了  我去用酒吧的电话吧
Fine, I'll use the phone at the bar.
兰吉特  请把隔离板拉起来
Ranjit, would you please put up the partition?
拉起隔离板
Partition going up.
你居然梦到和兰吉特亲热
You had a sex dream about Ranjit!
什么
Hello.
兰吉特
Ranjit!
抱歉
Sorry.
好吧  我承认  是有这回事
Okay, yes, I did,
这又没什么
but it didn't mean anything.
梦里到底发生了什么
Okay, well, what happened in this dream?
我要知道全部内容
And I want to know everything.
给我和盘托出
Every explicit detail.
不能漏掉任何细节
Don't leave out any...
我靠  兰吉特
Damn it, Ranjit!
抱歉
Sorry.
马修  那只是一个梦
Marshall, it was a dream.
梦反应的是
Yeah, well, dreams are just stuff
你潜意识想要发生的事情
that you subconsciously want to happen.
不然我为什么总是梦见
Why do you think I'm constantly dreaming
大脚野人担任维京橄榄球队的四分卫呢
about Bigfoot playing quarterback for the Vikings?
因为你看着那样的画入睡
Because you fall asleep looking at a painting of it.
那画能让我安详入睡
It soothes me.
别转移话题
Don't try to change the subject.
你"梦叛"了我
You sleep-cheated.
你梦叛我数次  跟无数人睡过了
You've been sleep-sleeping around,
我受够了
and I'm sick of it.
老娘真想一走了之
You know, I have half a mind to get out
大餐留给你一个人吃好了
and let you eat all by yourself.
我应该停车吗
Should I pull over?
我靠   兰吉特
Damn it, Ranjit!
行  兰吉特  停车
Yes, Ranjit. Pull over.
停车
Pulling over.
等着瞧吧  泰德
You watch, Ted.
今晚如果我们去偷骆驼
Tonight is going to be legen--
必将极富戏剧性
it's the night we stole a camel...
偷骆驼之夜
然后造就传奇的偷骆驼之夜
...which means it'll be full of drama-- dary.
"戏剧惊夜"[单峰骆驼]
Dromedary!
我折服于你的妙语如珠
I applaud your wordplay,
但你的中心思想漏洞百出
but your core premise is flawed.
不可能每个夜晚都是传奇之夜
Every night can't be legendary.
如果夜夜都是传奇
If all nights are legendary,
那传奇将不再传奇
no nights are legendary.
泰德  明白没  你这种态度
See, Ted, that attitude right there,
就是我领先的原因
that's why I'm in the lead.
你领先是什么意思
What do you mean, in the lead?
我说的是人生的游戏  泰德
I'm talking about the game of life, Ted.
计分板
Scoreboard.
服装比你强  75分
Better wardrobe: 75 points.
公寓所在楼层比你高  90分
Apartment on a higher floor: 90 points.
名字比你长  110分
Longer name: 110 points.
等等  这打分制度是你现拟的吧
Sorry. Did you just make up this point system?
拟制打分制度  114分
Made up the point system: 114 points.
被你发现了  奖你10分
And ten points to you for pointing that out.
干得漂亮  泰德
Nice job, Ted.
为我无私给你10分的举动
15 points to me for being gracious enough
我自己再加15分
to give you those ten points.
泰德  重点在这
But here's the point, Ted.
我每次出去欢度春宵时
Every time I go out and have an awesome night
你都没参与到
and you're not there,
这又给我带来100分
that's another 100 points in my column.
所以  不好意思  我领先
So yeah, I'm in the lead.
巴尼  我能整晚安心地待在家
Barney, the fact that I can stay home for a night
表示我拥有平静的内心
shows that I have inner peace
也不觉得自己需要记着破分数
and that I don't feel the need to keep score.
这起码值一千分了
That's worth like 1,000 points right there,
我们最多是平局
so at the very least, we're tied.
我们才没有平局[系上]
We're so not tied.
你知道什么是系上的吗
Although you know what is tied--
我女友身上的比基尼系带
the strap of my girlfriend's bikini.
有时候也没系  因为她是个脱衣舞女郎
Except when it's not, 'cause she's a stripper.
1百万分  胜负已定
One million points! Game.
结束了
It's over.
结束了  结束了
It's done. It's done.
你是做什么的
So what do you do?
你不是吧
You're kidding, right?
我  我是空中主播
I... I'm an on-air reporter.
五分钟前我刚做完一则报道
I just did a report like five minutes ago.
你听起来很挫败
You sound frustrated.
是的  没错
Yeah, I am.
使尽浑身力气  还是得不到认可
I'm busting my ass, and as usual, no recognition.
罗宾  我干这行好些年了
Robin, I've been doing this a while,
我学到了一件事  一切皆浮浮[浮云]
and if there's one thing I've learned, it's flarm.
-什么  -浮浮
- What? - Flarm.
浮浮  浮浮  浮浮
Flarm, flarm, flarm.
油问提
Blobbum.
你发什么神经啊
What is wrong with you?
你舌头中风吗
Are you having a stroke?
他确实中风了
As a matter of fact, he was.
别  别  等等
Oh! Hold on! Wait!
与此同时  莉莉急需一个女性朋友倾诉
Meanwhile, Lily was in desperate need of a female friend.
莉莉  我已经见怪不怪了
Lily, I have seen this a million times.
妻子一怀孕  男人就发疯
Guys go crazy when there's a baby on the way.
你应该看看经理妻子怀孕时他的反应
You should have seen the manager when his wife got pregnant.
才怀孕中期  他就不让她跳艳舞了
After the second trimester, he made her stop stripping.
对  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
现在我好难过
Now I feel bad.
我们的大餐被毁了
Our big dinner's been ruined.
马修现在可能正嚎啕大哭
Marshall's probably crying right now.
我真没想到食物居然能这么好吃
I had no idea that food could be this delicious.
马修  你这是在发疯
Marshall, you are being crazy.
不不  我能处理好的
No, no, I can handle it.
如果我卖了笔记本
If I sell my laptop,
就能再来一盘南瓜花
we can get seconds on those squash blossoms.
我是说莉莉
I mean about Lily.
她自己也在发疯啊
Well, you know, she's being crazy, too.
她怀孕了
She's pregnant.
她有权发疯
She gets to be crazy.
你得做理智的那一方
You have to be the sane one.
所以直到宝宝出生后
So what, I don't get to be crazy again
我才能卖疯吗
until the baby comes?
不  到时候就轮宝宝耍疯了
No. Then it's baby's turn to be crazy.
那什么时候才能轮到我发疯啊
When do I get to be crazy again?
没机会了
Never.
我们完全打平了
We are totally even.
我们绝对没有打平  原因在此
We absolutely are not even, and here's why.
我承认  如果把你
I'll grant you that if you include
设计摩天大楼得的12分
the 12 points for designing the skyscraper,
给汤米・李来个击"脸"得的83分
the 83 points for slapping five with Tommy Lee
在我之前推倒罗宾得的9000分加起来
and the 9,000 points for banging Robin before me,
我们的分数或许才有可能不相上下
our point totals would be about neck and neck,
但是你忘了一件事情
but there's one thing you're forgetting.
老子懒得鸟你吗
The fact that I don't care?
不是
No.
而且你刚刚顶嘴  扣掉5分
And you just lost five points for sass.
还记得三年前我们的一次谈话吗
Do you remember a conversation we had about three years ago?
巴尼  王中之王
Barney, you're the king.
手到妞来  无人可及
Nobody picks up chicks like you.
你英俊潇洒
You're handsome,
玉树临风
debonair,
是我梦寐以求的目标
everything I wish I could be.
我开始觉得是你在瞎吹了
I'm starting to think this never happened.
听你自己慢慢道来
Let you finish.
你处事圆滑  魅力超群
You're smooth, charismatic,
嗡嗡而痒
"Sauve."
你是想说"温文尔雅"吧
I think you mean "suave."
你果然记得那一晚
So you do remember.
但有一件事
But there's one thing
是连你这样的大情圣也无法完成的
even a master ladies' man like you could never do,
如果你做到了的话
and if you could ever do it,
就可获得500分
it would be worth 500 points.
愿闻其详  我那身高略矮的朋友
You have my attention, my slightly shorter friend.
这个挑战就是
Here's the challenge.
穿着裙子要到女生的电话
Get a girl's phone number while you're wearing a dress.
挑战
Challenge...
完成了
accomplished.
没有错
That's right.
去年  我随便套上一条裙子
Last year, I slapped on a dress,
在这酒吧里晃荡了几步
took a few laps around this very bar,
就拿到了
and I got this:
某个叫丝黛芬妮・麦考根的女人的电话
the phone number of one Stephanie McColgan.
那天晚上  我脱下了我的连裤袜
Later that night, I took off my pantyhose,
和她的"裤"里乾坤  "连"成一体
and gave her panties... my hose.
是的  泰德
That's right, Ted.
我领先了500分
I am 500 points ahead.
除非你也能穿着裙子要到女生的电话
Until you can get a girl's digits while wearing a dress,
否则你永远都赶不上我
you and I will never be even.
算了  管理员估计在等我了
You know what? The super's probably waiting for me,
而且我刚想起来  备用钥匙在门垫下
and I just remembered there's a spare key under the doormat,
-晚安了  -等等  泰德  先别走
- so good night. - Wait, wait. Ted, don't go.
巴尼  我要走了
Barney, I am leaving.
恐怕今晚也会成为众多被我们
I'm afraid this is just one of those nights
淡忘的夜晚之一了
we're probably going to forget.
我可不这么觉得  老弟  你看
I don't think so, dude. Look.
如果你刚开始收看本节目  环球新闻
If you're just joining us, the World Wide News
空中播报直升机在曼哈顿上空失控
eye in the sky traffic chopper is out of control over Manhattan
现在正由本台的罗宾・施巴斯基驾驶
and being piloted by our own Robin Scherbatsky.
估计会机毁人亡
This probably won't end well.
孩子们  纽约时不时就会出现
Kids, every now and then, New York has a moment
让全城人民共同关注一件事的时刻
when every eye in the city is watching the same thing.
今晚就是其中之一
This was one of those moments.
我们全都屏息观看地面上的飞行员
We all watched breathlessly as the pilot on the ground
指导着罗宾驾驶
told her what to do,
最后  突破了重重困难
and against all odds,
你们的罗宾阿姨成功着陆了
your Aunt Robin landed that helicopter.
我成功了
I did it.
I did it!
飞行员活了下来  并完全康复
The pilot survived and made a full recovery.
而罗宾呢
And Robin?
各位  罗宾・施巴斯基来了
It's Robin Scherbatsky, everybody!
多谢各位
Thank you so much.
别  别
Oh, okay...
罗宾一夜成名
Robin got famous.
接下来几天里  她将会
In the next few days, she would...
被市长接见
meet the Mayor,
登上莱特曼晚间秀
go on Letterman
甚至还拥有了以她命名的熟食三明治
and even have a deli sandwich named after her.
但最重要的是  那天晚上
But most importantly, that night,
几乎所有认识她的人都给她
she got a call, text or e-mail
打来了电话  发来了短信或邮件
from almost everyone she'd ever met.
马修啊
Hey, Marshall.
莉莉啊
Hey, Lil.
巴尼啊
Hey, Barney.
是  我知道你的女朋友是脱衣舞娘
Yes, I know you're dating a stripper.
老爸啊
Hey, Dad.
为你家姑娘感到骄傲不
You proud of your little girl?
好吧  我会继续努力的
Okay, I'll keep trying.
亲爱的  我知道你为什么
Babe, I think I know why you had
-做春梦会梦到兰吉特了  -为什么
- that sex dream about Ranjit. - Why?
你想想看
Think about it.
他谈起自己孩子时慈爱的表情
The way he talks about his kids.
简直就是个模范老爹啊
He's a wonderful father.
就跟蓝精灵爸爸  比尔・科斯比一样
Just like Papa Smurf, Bill Cosby...
还有乔治・华盛顿  我们的国父
George Washington, the father of our country.
你对“好爸爸”情有独钟
You're attracted to great dads.
所以你才会爱上我
And that's why you love me.
因为我将成为史上最好最棒的爸爸
Because I'm going to be the greatest dad ever.
没错  肯定是这个原因
Sure, that must be it.
莉莉决定不告诉马修
Lily decided not to tell Marshall
她也曾梦见和科学怪人
about her dream involving Frankenstein
还有《美女与野兽》中的小茶杯缠绵的事
and the tea cup from Beauty and the Beast.
这是属于她的小秘密
That one was just for her.
巴尼  我该走了
Okay, Barney, I got to go.
什么
What?
今晚才过了一半
In the middle of
这个"你穿着睡衣被锁在门外
"The Night You Got Locked Out in Your Pajamas
罗宾成功降落了直升机
"And Robin Landed a Freaking Helicopter
而我们还有时间重组创世纪乐团"之夜
and There's Still Time to Reunite Genesis?"
你穿着睡衣被锁在门外
罗宾成功降落了直升机
老兄  你的愿望已经达成了
Dude, you got your wish.
我们将永远铭记今夜
It's a night we'll always remember.
何不就此回家呢
Why can't we just go home?
-我不能回家  泰德  -为什么
- I can't go home, Ted. - Why not?
因为  我的女友是脱衣舞娘
Because... I'm dating a stripper.
是  我看见你那公车广告了
Yes, I've seen your bus ad.
我知道
I get it.
不  你不知道
No, you don't.
每天晚上  从9点到凌晨4点
Every night, between 9:00 P.M. and 4:00 A.M.,
我像活在人间地狱里
I'm in hell.
脑中所想  尽是昆茵在干什么
All I can think about is what Quinn is doing
在哪里干  在谁身上干
and where she is doing it and who she is doing it on.
不做别的事来忘却忧愁的话...
If I don't do something to take my mind off of it...
能安稳的想宅就宅  也是种幸福  泰德
You're lucky that you can just go sit around the house, Ted.
而我却没有这幸福的权力
I don't have that option.
你真的爱上了这个女孩
You're in love with this girl.
是的  泰德
I really am, Ted.
毕竟...
I mean...
她可是个脱衣舞娘
she's a stripper.
那天晚上晚些时候
Later that night...
泰德
我知道
我们现在不再联系...
但我想
让你知道...
你能平安无事
我很开心
隔天晚上
The next night,
我只想要好好待在家里一晚
all I wanted to do was enjoy a night at home.
但有件事我不得不去做
But there was something I had to do.
这是个艰难的挑战
It wasn't easy,
好
Okay.
现在我们打成平手了
Now we're even.
500分
500 points.
记分板
Scoreboard.
比起一个令人永远铭记的传奇之夜
More than a legendary night we'd remember forever,
巴尼叔叔更需要兄弟来让他忘却烦恼
Uncle Barney needed a bro to help him forget.
而这次  则是一个穿着裙子的兄弟
In this case, a bro in a dress.
我为你感到骄傲
I'm proud of you.
你擦了香水吗
Are you wearing perfume?
是男女皆可用的香氛  《细节》都有提过
It's a unisex fragrance. It was in Details.
美国男性时尚杂志
-挺好闻的  -其实就是香水
- It's nice. - It's perfume.